

# **CRISTIANA VIEIRA**

# DEGREE IN MARKETING AND ADVERTISING

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Hi, my name is Cristiana, I'm 23 years old and I consider myself an organized, committed, empathetic and communicative person. I'm always looking for continuous improvement and personal development with focus on my goals and aiming to achieve good results. I'm motivated to continue self developing on either my personal and professional perspectives.

#### CONTACTS

- Rebordosa-Paredes
  Porto, Portugal
- cristiana.marketeer@gmail.com
- 910 25 45 70
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/cristiana vieira2403/
- © @cristianavieira.pt
- https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100086210201438

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### September 2022- Present

#### **GUIPER- Wholesale Building Materials, Porto**

Monitor and identify market trends and opportunities; Preparation of graphic materials; Define and implement digital marketing communication strategies; Ensuring the continuous quality, relevance and adequacy of the contents disclosed in the communication channels; Monitor results of all marketing activities; Plan, develop, implement and manage content for the digital channels Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn; Benchmarking; Competition Analysis; Daily use of CRM (Hubspot), also providing training to the company's employees on the respective customer relationship management platform.

# RESPONSIBLE FOR MARKETING AND COMMUNICATION - FULL TIME JOB

#### February 2022- May 2022

#### Up We Go- Digital Marketing Agency, Porto

Management of Social Networks like Facebook, LinkedIn and Instagram (Swonkie and Meta Business Suite)

Content Writing (Blog Posts, Websites, Posts For Social Networks, Magazines, Ebooks, Brochures, Formal Documents For Clients) Competition Analysis

Benchmarking

Usability Tests (Mobile & Desktop)

Implementation of content on The website (WordPress)

Newsletters funcionality tests

#### **MARKETING ASSISTANT- INTERN**

19 VALUES.

August 2018- August 2019
O Meu Sorriso Clínicas
DENTAL ASSISTANT- FULL TIME JOB

April 2018 - June 2018 Trofa Saúde - Hospital Privado de Alfena HEALTHCARE ASSISTANT AT EXTERN CONSULTATIONS-INTERN 18 VALUES.

May 2017 - June 2017 Lar São Lourenço, Ermesinde HEALTHCARE ASSISTANT - INTERN

18 VALUES.

#### HOBBIES

- Travel
- Sport
- Photography
- Films
- Music
- · Read magazines and blogs from different areas
- · Do online courses
- Participate in Workshops

## DRIVING LICENSE



Category B since 2018

#### EDUCATION

#### **Digital Marketing & Strategy Course**

EDIT.- Disruptive Digital Education, Porto

Program: Digital Strategy; E-commerce; Platforms and websites; SEO & SEA; Metrics and Analytics; Email Marketing; Display Advertising; Social Media; 360° Digital Project.

March 2023- July 2023

#### **Degree in Marketing and Advertising**

ISCET, Instituto Superior de Ciências Empresariais e do Turismo

2019-2022 Grade: 16

#### **Health Assistant-Level 4 Professional Course**

Escola Profissional de Valongo

2015-2018

Final project: 20 Values Final grade: 17 Values

#### CERTIFICATES

- · Digital Marketing Google Atelier Digital
- Content Marketing Basics Great Learning
- Social Media Management- Elife & BuzzMonitor
- Google Analytics for Beginners Google Analytics Academy
- · Copywriting for conversions: How to Write Persuasive Content - Alison
- Inbound Marketing HubSpot Academy
- · Creative Writing and Storytelling for Local Businesses -Maia City Council and Rural Coast
- Emotional Photography for Business Maia City Council and **Rural Coast**
- Creative Photography for Local Businesses Maia City Council and Rural Coast
- Introduction to Digital Marketing for Businesses Mentor Maria Gonçalves

#### LANGUAGES

- · Portuguese Native Language
- English Intermediate

### SOFT AND HARD SKILLS

- · Good interpersonal relationships
- Good presentation and diction
- · Good interaction and communication skills
- Good ability to work in a group
- Good capacity for autonomy and personal organization
- Good time management skills
- · Ability to work under pressure
- · Problem solving ability
- Mastery of Office, Canva, Hubspot, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Asana, Swonkie, Etus, Meta Business Suite, Miro, GoVisually and Wordpress
- Knowledge of Instagram, Facebook and LinkedIn Ads

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

**2012:** Dancer

2015: Handball player

2016-2018: Swimmer and gym workout

2019-2022: Delegate of the 1st, 2nd and 3rd year of the Degree in

Marketing and Advertising

**2021 and 2022**: Representative member of the Degree in Marketing and Advertising at the Pedagogical Council of ISCET

**2021:** Publication of the article "Artificial intelligence and the impact on marketing and the consumer" in the Scientific Journal of ISCET Percursos & Ideias number 11 - 2nd series 2021

**2022:** Article writing "The impact of influencers on purchase intent in the transition from fast fashion to slow fashion" in the subject "Research Project"